[Music]
[音乐]
you
您
hi welcome to new every day my name is
嗨， 欢迎来到 我的名字是 新的 每一天
Carrie my name is Jen and on today's
嘉莉我的名字是仁和今天的
show we're going to talk about hey you
表明我们要谈谈你嘿
know what God really does answer prayer
知道神真的回答了祷告
so stay tuned we write back
敬请关注我们回信
[Music]
[音乐]
turn
转
hey and welcome back to new every day
嘿，欢迎回到新的每一天
the wedding is tuned in we're still on
婚礼正在调整中，我们仍在继续
the road we've now gone through
我们现在走过的道路
Tennessee and we're in Kentucky headed
田纳西州和我们在肯塔基州率先
back home to Canada and we have had a
回到加拿大的家， 我们有一个
great American experience hey guys like
伟大的美国经验嘿家伙喜欢
so I may say so it wasn't as creating oh
所以我可以这样说，这不是创造哦
yeah okay so what was one of the
没关系，那是什么
highlights of your overall like American
你的整体像美国人的亮点
experience my overall American
体验我的整体美国人
experience one of them was going to the
经历其中一人正在去
country music hall of fame and museum
乡村音乐名人堂和博物馆
which for me was just so amazing because
这对我来说太棒了，因为
I was raised on country music and
我被提到了乡村音乐和
bluegrass when my dad looks into a whole
当我父亲看到一个整体时，蓝草
bunch of different flavors of music and
一群不同风格的音乐和
so going there was just a really cool
所以去那里真的很酷
opportunity to I want to relive my
我想 重温我的 机会
childhood go oh yeah I've heard these
童年去哦是的，我听说过这些
guys I saw them on TV and my first
我 在电视和我的第一次看到他们
concert was my dad taking me to the
演唱会是我爸带我去的
memorial center in Kingston Ontario for
纪念中心在金斯顿安大略为
the Oakridge boys and so to go to the
奥克里奇男孩等等去了
museum and see I want to say they're
博物馆，看看我想说他们是
their star or their plaque on the wall
他们的明星或他们的牌匾在墙上
is inducted into the Hall of Fame which
被引入到名人堂当中
is like like right now those times are
就像现在这些时间一样
you and so
你等等
being there and then doing the Grand Old
在那里，然后做 Grand Old
Opry the Grand Ole Opry was really seen
大奥普里的Opry真的被看到了
it was at the Ryman for the next couple
它是在下一对夫妇的莱曼
of weeks it'll be air over Christmas
几个星期它会在圣诞节结束
time and yeah what an amazing old church
时间和耶是一个了不起的老教堂
and the sound was incredible and see
声音令人难以置信，看到了
live music is always so much better than
现场音乐总是比这更好
like I can't name the concert oh yeah
就像我无法命名音乐会哦，是的
that was really good so now that was my
那真的很好，所以现在是我的了
sort of highlight of Nashville now what
纳什维尔现在什么样的亮点
was your highlight of Nashville oh love
是你纳什维尔噢爱的亮点
Nashville oh it would break a party it
纳什维尔哦，它会打破一个派对
was a party scene it was overwhelming
是一个派对场面，它是压倒性的
the number of people who were downtown
市中心的人数
because there was a consequent on
因为有一个随之而来的
football game all this job and screaming
足球比赛所有这个工作和尖叫
but for my American experience
但为了我的 美国经历
chick-fil-a it right up there okay so
鸡 -  fil  - 它正确的那里没关系
for our viewers what is chick-fil-a well
对于我们的观众来说，什么是小鸡 - 好
it's my fast food is like fried chicken
这是我的快餐就像炸鸡
projek advantages and it was really do
projek的优势， 这是真的
they have this really cool like honey
他们像蜂蜜一样非常酷
mustard no potato the author's
芥末不是土豆的作者
mayonnaise dip sauce and it was like
蛋黄酱蘸酱，就像
hello and waffle fry oh I don't eat that
你好，华夫饼炒哦，我不吃那个
food very often but let me tell you it
食物很多，但让我告诉你
was good it was great and I went up to
很好， 很棒，我去了
the financially by some sauce and take
经济上由一些酱和拿
it back
它回来了
the guy kind of looked at me from
那家伙从我面前看着我
anything well we've got eight ounce tubs
我们有8盎司的浴缸
I said I'll take it it was great those
我说我会认为这是很棒的
in the cooler in the back I'm sure we'll
在后面的冷却器中， 我相信我们会的
be enjoying it in the dates announced
在宣布的日期享受它
yet but anyways but when we really
但无论如何， 但当我们真的
actually like so we talked to overall
实际上就像我们所谈论的那样
highlight of the American experience but
美国经验的亮点
what's really interesting if you were to
如果你愿意，真的很有趣
ask us what our highlights were was
问我们的亮点是什么
really God answering prayer and and
真正的上帝回答祈祷和
that's what this should be titled the
这就是这应该被称为
show is you know fine really doesn't
表演是你知道的罚款真的没有
answer prayer and you might be wow what
回答祷告，你可能会 哇
are you glad to see you guys and the
你很高兴 见到你们和你们
answer is we speak we prayed simple
答案是我们说我们祈祷简单
prayers every morning God would you
每天早上你都会祈祷上帝
bring up the people that you want us to
培养你想要我们的人
interact with today and would you direct
与今天互动， 你会直接指导
our steps we to direct our conversations
我们的步骤来指导我们的对话
and I got I post a lot on facebook when
我在facebook上发布了很多内容
we're on vacation one I guess so people
我们正在度假，我猜是这样的人
know that we're alive and we're safe and
知道我们还活着，我们很安全
also just to share with people back home
也只是为了与人分享回家
about what we're doing and a lot of
关于我们在做什么 和很多
people enjoy watching our trips so that
人们喜欢看我们的旅行，所以
being said a friend of mine messaged me
被说是我的一个朋友给我发消息
and said are you guys going to be in
并说你们会进去的
Nashville or when you're going to be in
纳什维尔或者你什么时候进去
Nashville and I said well Friday and he
我和纳什维尔星期五说好了，他
said yeah we're coming through and now
说是啊，我们要来通过和现在
you guys have met Jared Clark before
你们之前见过杰瑞德克拉克
who's been on the show talking about
谁一直在节目中谈论
camp and they're from Winnipeg and we're
他们来自温尼伯，我们是
from ontario toronto and so when you
从安大略多伦多，所以当你
actually do the math it was twenty
实际上做了二十的数学
four-hour drive between toronto canada
加拿大多伦多之间的四小时车程
winnipeg manitoba and so I only get to
温尼伯马尼托巴，所以我只得到
see them once a year and carrie has a
每年看一次， 嘉莉有一次
semen in about two years and so they
大约两年的精液，所以他们
were driving through at the same time
正在同时开车
and judge in Nashville and national
并在纳什维尔和全国进行评判
values and so they have for young kids
价值观，所以他们对年幼的孩子
and Hannah one of their daughters said
汉娜的一个女儿说
to them Hoshi you know she coming to see
对他们来说， 你知道她会来看看
I and the mom said well no God just
我和妈妈说没有神
worked this out and it's so true like I
解决了这个问题，和我一样真实
would say that was one of the highlights
会说这是亮点之一
just to see how God works at all
只是为了看看上帝是如何工作的
together and spending that time with
一起度过这段时光
family and we can twist the back when
家庭，我们可以扭转背部时
god you're so good like so good and we
上帝，你是如此的好，我们
had to meet in the state even though
曾在状态迎接即使
we're both from Canada yeah it was
我们都来自加拿大，是的
really a wonderful time so yeah we went
真的是美好的时光，所以我们去了
to hang out with the Clark family yeah
和克拉克家人一起出去玩
then before the last night which was
然后在昨天晚上之前
Saturday to me yep we are in the hotel
周六对我来说，我们是在酒店
room and just praying and we're looking
房间，只是祈祷，我们正在寻找
for a church to go to and yeah done with
一个教会去，是的
googling churches and you ended up
谷歌搜索教堂，你结束了
finding one yes and I had typed in Free
找到一个是的，我输入了Free
Methodist churches we're a part of the
我们是卫理公会教堂的一部分
president's nomination and for some of
总统的提名和一些
you might be thinking what is that well
你可能在想什么是好的
maybe we'll do a show on that at a later
也许我们稍后会做一个展示
time but you can just google for
时间，但你可以只是谷歌
methodist church in canada and go to
加拿大卫理公会教堂， 并 去
what we believe and you can check it out
我们相信，你 可以检查出来
in and some evangelical church and we
在和一些福音派教会和我们
believe in the Apostles Creed and
相信 使徒信经和
anyways moving on I always liked
反正继续我总是喜欢
different methodist churches and so i
不同的 教派教堂，所以 我
googled it for methodist churches near
在附近用卫理公会教会搜索它
us and there was one three and a half
我们和那里有一个三分之一
hours away and I said oh kehri three and
几个小时的路程，我说哦kehri三和
a half hours late but I recognize it
迟了半小时，但我承认它
it's in Wilmore Kentucky associated with
它在Wilmore肯塔基州与
the Asbury University University and
阿斯伯里大学和阿斯伯里大学
Seminary it's a free methodist
神学院是一个免费的卫道士
university in seminary would be really
在神学院的大学将是真的
cool and she's like oh yeah I'm totally
很酷，她喜欢噢，我完全
up for it so I'm like yeah okay so we
为了它，所以我喜欢耶，所以我们
got up at five o'clock this morning
今天早上五点起床
asian we traveled for three and a half
亚洲人我们旅行了三年半
hours to go to church when you might be
你可能会 去教堂的 时间
me that's crazy that drives three and a
我疯了，推动三个和一个
half hours to church and yet I knew as
半小时到教堂，但我知道
soon as Kerry said oh yeah i'm in for
克里说，噢，我是为了
i'm like okay then let's go I knew it
我很好，那我们走吧，我知道 了
would have been all I wanted to say one
本来就是我想说的一个
of because of the college's associated
因为大学的联系
or because the church is associated with
或者因为教会与之相关
college I I knew that there would just
大学二知道会有
be
是
it would be a great place to attend and
这将是一个很好的参加和参观的地方
so I'm like okay no problem let's let's
所以我好像没问题让我们来吧
set the timer for five o'clock and so
将计时器设置为五点钟等等
and what's interesting is this is what
有趣的是这是什么
Kerry prayed before he went to bed yeah
凯瑞在睡觉前祈祷耶
I agree that it would be a good
我同意这将是一件好事
experience of being with other people in
与其他人在一起的经历
the church and that we'd be able to have
教堂和 我们能够 拥有的
lunch with someone from the church
和 教堂里的 人共进午餐
because I wanted to be able to start
因为我希望 能够启动
with them and connect with them and I
与他们并与他们和我联系
said Jen wouldn't that be cool if maybe
说，如果可能 仁那不是 很酷
we're going to go for lunch of them
我们打算去吃 午饭
because she loves doing things like that
因为她喜欢做那样的事情
and then i'll have the reasons why she's
然后我会有她为什么的原因
my friend she teaches me about having a
我的朋友，她教我有一个
greater heart for people and and so
对于人们而言更大的心脏等等
we're going to tell you about the
我们会告诉你关于
answers of that prayer right after that
在那之后，那个祷告的答案
so stay tuned Jeff Weston Gemma you're
所以请继续关注Jeff Weston Gemma
building a brand new beautiful website
建立一个全新的美丽网站
what are you all right you're terrible
你很好，你很可怕
actor what this we're acting comes into
演员我们正在演戏的是什么
play oh I don't know where Isaac you're
玩哦，我不知道艾萨克在哪里
supposed to act okay fair enough I
应该足够公平地表现我的行为
really building a really cool website
真的建立一个非常酷的网站
are you building a really cool website
你在建立一个非常酷的网站吗？
you need hosting one of the things about
你需要托管其中的一件事
a hosting account is you don't want to
一个托管账户是你不想要的
have limitations put on your website
对您的网站有限制
it's sure how much hard drive space you
它确定你有多少硬盘空间
have how many email accounts how many
有多少电子邮件帐户有多少个
domains can point to it well we've got
域可以指向我们已有的
an amazing deal for you for a very
对于你来说，这是一笔惊人的交易
limited time cap five dot TV / dreamhost
限时五顶点电视/ dreamhost
for just five dollars and a bit of
只有五美元和一点点
change per month you are going to get
每个月你会 得到更改
unlimited web site hosting unlimited
无限的网站托管无限
email accounts on that hosting service
该托管服务上的电子邮件帐户
you are also going to receive a free
你也会收到免费的
domain name the roof of your own com
域名是您自己com的屋顶
dice to put that amazing website that
骰子把那个惊人的网站，
you've been working on on there if you
你一直在那里工作，如果你
run if you want to build a wordpress
运行， 如果你想建立一个wordpress
site fine sign up cat five gb flash
网站罚款注册猫五GB闪存
dream hope still fulfill the papers are
梦想的希望仍然履行论文被
just don't do it but hey I
只是不要这样做，但嘿我
it's a great deal folk best deal you're
这是一个很好的民间 最佳交易
going to find five dollars and change
去找五块钱并改变
per month go to cap five TV / dreamhost
每个月去上限五个电视/ dreamhost
hey and welcome back to new every day
嘿，欢迎回到新的每一天
we're still on the road in Kentucky and
我们仍然在肯塔基州和美国的道路上
we're talking about how God has answered
我们谈论 神如何回答
our prayers in meeting with different
我们的祈祷与不同的会面
people on our trip and you know it is a
我们旅行的人， 你知道这是一个
wonderful experience firstly I want to
首先我想要的是美妙的体验
thank the people already in our life
感谢已经在我们生活中的人们
Robbie Ferguson and the teams from
罗比弗格森和来自世界各地的球队
category 5 thank you for making this
类别5感谢你做出这一点
show possible and if you would like to
显示可能的，如果你想
help continue to make this show possible
帮助继续使这个节目成为可能
and we ask the you are Carter stage new
我们问你是卡特舞台新的
everyday TV and scroll down through look
每日电视，并向下滚动看看
at the different organizations and
在不同的组织和机构
businesses supporting us and if you can
支持我们的企业，如果可以的话
support us by supporting them that was
通过支持我们来支持我们
so thank you thank you yes so we are
所以谢谢你是的，所以我们是
going to the free methodist church in
去英国免费的卫理公会教堂
Wilmore in Kentucky and I prayed God it
我在肯塔基州的威尔莫尔和我一起向上帝祈祷
would be really great to have lunch with
吃午饭真的很棒
someone and mention it to Jen so after
有人 在Jen之后提及它
service Jen talk to the pastor and we
Jen服务人员与牧师和我们谈话
end up meeting with someone that you
最终会见你的人
know so a friend of mine in Jones old
在琼斯老朋友那里知道我的朋友
house who are pastors in the true
真正牧师的房子
Methodist Church and I've known them
卫理公会教会和我认识他们
forever and ever as long as I've been
永远和永远，只要我一直
alive anyway to sister is a prof at the
无论如何活到姐姐是一名教授
school and I totally remember that when
学校，我完全记得 那时
I got to church and I was like hey I
我去了教堂，我就像嘿我
should probably stop to at least
应该至少停下来
introduce myself and so the pastor
介绍我自己和牧师
introduces us and as we get chatting
介绍我们和我们聊天
seems like do you have any plans for
好像你有任何计划
lunch and inside of me I'm going Terry
午餐和我内心我要去特里
is going to love this
会喜欢这个
if she's like I like to have time for a
如果她像我喜欢有时间的话
historical experience and once again
历史经验和再次
Kari he is going too long and on the
卡里，他太长了，在上
outside like yes I think that would be
外面像是，我认为那会是
lovely and on the inside i like doing
可爱和 内心我喜欢做
flip-flops going here he's going to love
人字拖到这里他会爱上
this period from period two steps away
这段时间距离两步之遥
for a few minutes in stuff when she came
在她来的时候几分钟
back I said you know dr. stone houses
我说你知道博士。石头房子
asked me if we would join her for lunch
问我是否会和她一起吃午饭
crisis yes and so then she let a pile on
危机是的，然后她让一堆
her car and he drove us Shaker Village a
她的车，他开车给我们沙克尔村
historical site we had a beautiful life
历史遗迹，我们有美好的生活
and she said please come as my guest and
她说，请作为我的客人来
she never met us never know I guess I'm
她从未见过我们，我从来不知道我猜我是
just as great and she's welcome welcome
同样伟大，她欢迎欢迎
right intimate for lunch talked about
右贴心的午餐谈起
the history of the area answer some of
该地区的历史回答了 一些
our other questions about the face of a
我们约的脸上其他问题
politics of not how she teaches about
而不是她如何教的政治
child development and have it here
儿童发展，并在这里
children can include them in ministry
孩子们可以把他们包括 在事工中
with a great conversation but what I
与一个伟大的谈话，但我的
really appreciated it was the
真的很感激它是
hospitality messy awkward yes and that's
招待凌乱尴尬是的， 就是这样
something that like I've been charged
像我已经 收费的东西
universal I think has set us apart yeah
我认为普遍性使我们与众不同
when we have people coming in like you
当我们有人像你一样进来时
kind of welcome them in and love them
欢迎他们并热爱他们
and and I just felt so loved by her
而且我只是觉得她很爱她
because there was no such as that of
因为没有那样的
adult well Foxman no it was just yep for
成人和福克斯曼不，它只是 为了
coming for lunch and the time that I
午餐时间和我的时间
have had people do that in my life it
有人在我的生活中这样做
has really been meaningful to me because
对我来说真的有意义，因为
I thoughts in front of us
我的想法在我们面前
yes they want to if they're inviting me
是的，他们想要如果他们邀请我
in and I want to offer that was someone
我想提供那个人
else's make them feel that way and it
其他的让他们有这样的感觉， 它
was interesting that what the sermon was
有趣的是 什么讲道
about maybe i'll let you talk about that
关于也许我会让你谈论这个
later 10 but the pastor said will what
后来10但牧师说会怎么样
are Christians here for it does not help
是基督徒在这里没有帮助
other people and that's one way that I
其他人，这是我的一种方式
feel like the church really has offered
感觉像教堂真的提供
to help other people and when they get
帮助其他人，当他们得到
to our door w offer them hospitality and
给我们的门提供他们的待客和
no question that and what's interesting
毫无疑问，有趣的是什么
when we spent the day with Jared and
当我们与Jared和
Becky you originally asked for what do
贝基你最初问的是什么
you mean on Thursday and it worked out
你的意思是在星期四，它解决了
to friday because we said we'll be in
到星期五，因为我们说我们会进来
nashville on friday but then they have
纳什维尔星期五， 但他们有
worked for small kids but they were
为小孩子工作，但他们是
willing to spend the whole day with us
愿意与我们共度一整天
like we met them about a lot of time and
就像我们遇到他们很多时间一样
we you know went to the museum with them
我们知道你和他们一起去了博物馆
and and talked about it and then we had
并且谈论了它，然后我们有了
to suffer together and even though we
一起遭受，即使我们
had separate like 730 I was like the
像730 一样分开。 我就像那样
Infante 830 like they were willing to
Infante 830就像他们愿意的那样
put their plans on order like no no
把他们的计划按照不不不
don't worry about and we kept saying
不要担心，我们一直在说
like if you need to go there once oh the
就好像 你需要 去那里一次哦
place on the thing oh he's about 380
放在东西上哦，他 大约是 380
yeah and he fell asleep on the table and
是的，他 在桌子上睡着了
who were just like oh my I know but they
谁只是喜欢哦， 我 ，但我知道他们
were still so willing and I'm so
仍然如此愿意，我是如此
grateful for that and it goes back to
感谢这一点，它可以追溯到
what Kerry said that more idea of of
克里说什么更多的想法
church family right because we we are
教会家庭权利，因为我们是
not blood related to the clarks we're
不是与我们的克拉克相关的血液
not blood related to dr. stone house not
不是与dr有关的血液。石屋不是
even blood related between us and yet
甚至血液与我们之间的关系
that whole idea of
那整个想法
oh I want to say being willing to hang
哦，我想说，愿意挂
out to put aside your own plan we're
放下你自己的 计划，我们是
building relationship for showing
建立关系展示
hospitality for showing love yeah and I
好客为显示爱是和我
thought about that I actually ran into
想到我真的遇到了
someone in the summer an old teacher
夏天有人是老教师
high school teacher of mine who said
我的高中老师说
that she wants to always be ready to
她想要随时准备好
have people over which doesn't mean have
有超过的人并不意味着有
you clean house and doesn't always mean
你打扫房子并不总是意味着什么
having good food in the fridge that if
如果在冰箱里有美味的食物
if people are willing to come and be
如果人们愿意来
with our family and we're going to have
与我们的家人 ，我们将会有
peanut butter gym and which is that's
花生酱健身房，这是这
what I'm going to put out and we're just
我什么都放出来，我们只是
going to be together and I just love
要在一起 ，我非常 喜欢
that picture
那张照片
they ready and willing ready and willing
他们已经准备好并乐意做好准备
and even as we came into the church
甚至当我们进入教会时
today I get older it's really hard for
今天我变老了真的很难
me amber little late but a little lady
我琥珀迟了一点，但一个小女人
right Matt eyes and she was so gracious
对马特的眼睛，她是如此亲切
because we said we're going on where we
因为我们说我们正在我们的地方
back on time said well eventually
准时回来说好了
they're going to be right here but right
他们会在这里， 但是正确的
now you have to go down the hall and did
现在你不得不走下大厅去做
it and she was just so yeah this is
但她只是太是啊，这是
coloring waited kind yes you know and
着色等着你是否知道和
the pastor went out of his way to
牧师走出去了
actually will come back in and I'll
实际上会回来 ，我会的
introduce you and and and he was just so
介绍你和和他就是 如此
very kind to stand there and talk with
非常善良的站在那里和交谈
us and that boy idea of hospitality yes
我们和那个男孩好客的想法是
I believe because we get so busy we
我相信因为我们太忙了
forget about I want to not much always
忘记我想永远不会太多
forget about we don't think we can put
忘记我们认为我们不能放
our own plans on laws because we think
因为我们认为我们自己的法律计划
that our our plans need to get done or
我们的计划需要完成或
some hunters are so exhausted and so
一些猎人如此疲惫等等
tired that we just can't seem to fathom
厌倦了我们似乎无法理解
I want they're putting at the time or
我希望他们在那个 时候或之后
energy to actually show hospitality to
能量实际上表现出热情好客
people and yet that's one of the things
人们，但这是其中的一件事
that I've appreciated about being in the
我很欣赏在这里
south is that wow they're not
南是那个哇，他们不是
necessarily in a hurry to get things
一定是急着拿东西
done soon everyone stops like they want
很快就完成了每个人都喜欢他们要的
to talk to us yes i did i get nice and
与 我们 交谈 是的，我做了我很好，并且
my next in line you can even lay out
我的下一个，你甚至可以布局
where are you from pretty no blind
你从哪里来，绝不盲目
people see i never want to have an
人们看到我从不想拥有一个
agenda that i think is so important and
议程，我认为是如此重要和
i'm not going to sell for that one
我不会 为一个卖
person we talked about the past the hell
我们谈到了过去的地狱
meaningful it is to stop and recognize
有意义的是停下来认识
the person in front of you yes
在你面前的人是的
and like several times as we've been
和像几次，因为我们已经
checking in and you're going to notice
登记入住，你会注意到
very much about my personality I like to
非常了解我的个性 ， 我喜欢
get things done which is a good thing
把事情做好 是件好事
otherwise we'd never get things done and
否则我们永远无法完成任务
the Lord has very graciously left me
主已非常优雅地离开了我
with a friend / coho who genuinely is
与一个真正的朋友/ coho
interested in people and every single
感兴趣的人和每一个
person who went to check us in engages
谁去 的人 来检查我们的啮合
in conversation and I'm standing there
在谈话中，我站在那里
and I'm watching Kerri pause and
我正在看着Kerri停下来
conversate back and forth and I'm like
来回转移，我很喜欢
lord I need to grasp this I need to
主我需要把握这个我需要的
grasp the importance of loving someone
把握爱一个人的重要性
the importance of pausing that may be
暂停的重要性可能是
important to us
对我们很重要
looking someone in the face and engaging
看着别人在脸上和参与
with them like that is a real person on
与他们一样，这是一个真正的人
the other side of that counter who
那个柜台的另一边是谁
actually probably appreciates a good
实际上可能会赞赏一件好事
conversation right with a kindness and
对话与善良和善良
love and so I'm watching these
爱，所以我正在看这些
conversations and it didn't just happen
谈话并不只是发生
once it happened time and time again and
一旦它发生一次又一次， 并且
I remember and yesterday I'm finial side
我记得，昨天我是最终的一方
by the cotton I'm thinking hearing went
由我认为听到的棉花去了
on catching to do I don't remember we
在追赶我不记得我们
went back important point printed any
回到重要的地方 打印任何
Rangers Debbie really wasn't a ranger
游骑兵黛比确实不是游侠
because color is it I have people named
因为颜色是我有人命名的
we get and so anyways been waiting and I
我们得到了，所以无论如何一直在等待着我
just I'm I'm pepto some flowers I've
就我而言，我正在 尝试 一些花
gone around the other flower bed checked
去了另一个花床检查
out the flowers I'm almost close to
我几乎接近花儿
counting the bricks on the wall that's
计算墙上的砖块
not really but I'll catch up yet anyways
不是真的，但我会赶上反正
finally I go back in and there's Carrie
终于我回到了那里，还有嘉莉
talking to this gentleman
与这位绅士交谈
that makes sense a problem wallet any
这是有道理的 钱包任何问题
luck go ahead tell your side stories we
好运继续讲述我们的故事
deliver who was he I don't know the
送他是我不认识的人
owner of the oh yeah he was the owner of
哦，他是老板的主人
the hotel which was great and he comes
酒店很棒，他来了
Toronto every year to buy mangoes was
多伦多每年都会购买 芒果
great combination but you know what
伟大的组合，但你知道什么
exactly I think in the church family the
正是我认为在教会家庭中
burger to build community oh and the
汉堡建立社区哦和
other thing the pastor said today we
牧师今天说的其他事情我们
were meeting some part of Titus chapter
正在会见Titus章节的某些部分
one and we are to actually encourage
一个，我们实际上鼓励
each other step in our gifts that are
我们的礼物中的每一步都是这样
used to serve because yes like jam from
曾经服务，因为是喜欢果酱
the gift of being organized and setting
被组织和设置的礼物
an agenda helping people get there and
一个帮助人们到达那里的议程
recognizing kids and other people and
承认孩子和其他人和
helping those people to reach their
帮助这些人达到他们的目标
potential and if tend to organize
潜力和是否倾向于组织
opportunities we would connect people
我们将会连接人员的机会
right so I think it goes it goes both
对，所以我认为它走了 两边
ways and we need that ass right back so
方式， 我们需要这样的屁股回来
you know so this is part 1 of how God
你知道这是上帝的第一部分
ancestors we're going to bring part to
我们将要带入的祖先
see you
再见
but this whole idea of God provided
但这整个 上帝的 想法 提供
people like literally poured into our
人们喜欢从字面上涌入我们的
lives for like two very special time and
像两个非常特殊的时间和生活
also it's a lot aspects of hospitality
还有很多方面的款待
and the importance of of pausing and
和暂停的重要性
putting things on hold and engaging in
把事情搁置起来并参与进来
people and just like those things you
人，就像你的那些东西
know they like terranan Becky had for
知道他们喜欢贝基为之而生的terranan
their kids to look after and yet they
他们的孩子照顾，但他们
pause for us professor stone house you
为我们暂停教授石屋你
know he had so many other people she
知道他有 很多其他人
could have interacted with that day but
可能会与当天互动，但是
she said there's some fellow Canadian my
她说有一些加拿大人我的
God look at you you know i'm home to us
神看着你，你知道我是我们的家
like for lunch and then so then you know
像午餐，然后你知道
i'm looking at okay that person on the
我在 看那个人好
other side of you know whose check mrs.
你的另一边知道 谁的支票夫人。
i need to stop and pause and show them
我需要停下来停下来展示他们
love and and no realize that they're
爱和不知道 他们是
real person too which is really cool how
真正的人也是如此
God answered prayers to meet our needs
上帝回应祈祷以满足我们的需要
but in respect has now caught us even
但是现在甚至已经引起我们的注意
more about doing that for others yeah so
更多关于如何为别人做这样的事情
I guess the challenge you this week is
我猜这个星期你面临的挑战是
with regards to you know praying network
关于你知道祈祷网络
or bring to you the people you want me
或者把你想要我的人带给你
to interact with today and then trust
与今天互动，然后相互信任
but he's actually going to do it and it
但他实际上要做到这一点，它
will be really cool like your your God
将会像 你的上帝 一样非常酷
tank will be filled up but then how is
坦克将被填满，但后来如何
he then going to use you to pour into
然后他会用你的注入
other people so let's pray Heavenly
其他人，让我们祈祷天堂
Father I thank you so much that you do
父亲，我非常感谢你，
answer prayers and lord thank you for
回答祷告和领主谢谢你
dr. stone housing for the the Clark
博士。为克拉克石屋
family totally poured into us and then
家庭完全涌入我们然后
lord thank you so much for those people
主啊，非常感谢那些人
that we've met in the hotels and who you
我们在酒店见过面，你是谁
are just reminding us show love to and
只是提醒我们展示爱与
their father we we can get the rest of
他们的父亲，我们可以得到其余的
our thank you that you're a biscuit duck
我们感谢你，你是一个饼干鸭
if you can see your brain a specific
如果你能看到你的大脑特定的
watch play that for our viewers may
看我们的观众可能会玩的游戏
raise to the name of Jesus comment
提到耶稣的评论
comment thanks for tuning in to new
评论感谢调整到新的
every day we look forward to seeing in
我们每天都期待着看到
next week same time same place to every
下周同一时间到每一个地方
day GV have enough
一天的GV就够了
you
您
[Music]
[音乐]
p
p
you
您
[Music]
[音乐]